# Parsa Mofrad

# **Profile**

Passionate mechanical engineering and computer science student with 4 years experience in customer service and sales, currently working as an Al Analyst at Optible Al. Seeking to gain practical engineering experience, as well as leverage customer service expertise and sales skills in the field of engineering.

# **Experience**

Al Analyst and Customer Success, Optible Al, Adelaide

AUGUST 2022 - PRESENT

**Events and Logistics Manager, Adept, Adelaide** 

AUGUST 2022 - PRESENT

Frontline Supervisor, YMCA Victoria, Adelaide

DECEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

Membership Service Officer, YMCA Victoria

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

# **Education**

Glenunga International High School

2016 - 2020

Bachelor of Engineering (Honours) (Mechanical) with Bachelor of Mathematical and Computer Sciences, The University of Adelaide

FEBRUARY 2021 - PRESENT

Chinese First Year. PACE. Adelaide

APRIL 2022 - NOVEMBER 2022

## **Extra-curricular activities**

"All Environment Explorer" Project, Team Leader, Adept

JANUARY 2022 - PRESENT

Vehicle Dynamics Team Member, University of Adelaide Motorsport Team

FEBRUARY 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022

Warman Design and Build Competition Contender

MARCH 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

Piano Player, AMEB

2009 - PRESENT

3D Modelling and Printing Service

JANUARY 2021 - PRESENT

# **Courses and Qualifications**

#### **Details**

0450153209 mofradparsa@gmail.com

#### **Skills**

**Customer Service Skills** 

Advanced Technology Skills

Strong Mathematical Skills

Teamwork and Leadership Skills

CAD and 3D Printing Skills

### Languages

English

Farsi

Mandarin First Year

First Aid, FirstAidPro

CPR, FirstAidPro

Barista Training, Rio Coffee

Food Safety, EHA

**Full Criminal History Check** 

Safeguarding Children and Child Protection, YMCA

**Bullying and Harrassment, YMCA** 

Chinese First Year, PACE

MARCH 2022 - NOVEMBER 2022

# **Achievements**

MASA Mathematics Talent Quest, First Place

2020

**Tennis Division 3 Boys, EDTA Premiers** 

2018

Principal's Award for Outstanding Achievement in Year 12 Specialist Mathematics, Mathematical Methods, Physics, English, and Research Project

2020

**KUMON Advanced Student Honour Roll** 

2017

### References

Dr. Farima Vatandoust, Specialist Consultant Physician

farima.forooziya@sa.gov.au | 0413597225

Dr. Nasser Asgari, Lecturer at College of Science and Engineering from-Flinders University

nasser.asgari@flinders.edu.au | 0403317331

Dr. Shahraam Afshar from UniSA

Shahraam.AfsharVahid@unisa.edu.au | 0430022094